# Tim Park

(714) 944-3085 | timpark0807@gmail.com | github.com/timpark0807

### SUMMARY

**Objective** Developer with 1.5 years of full-stack experience looking for a Software Engineering role.

Languages Python, GoLang, Javascript, Typescript

Other AWS, React.js, Node.js, Django, Git, SQL, NoSQL, AJAX, Pandas, Redis, oAuth

Concepts Object Oriented Programming, Data Structures & Algorithms, Version Control, REST, CI/CD

## **EXPERIENCE**

Accountant II/Software Developer | Santa Barbara Auditor-Controller's Office | Aug 2017 - Present

- Built an automated data pipeline to streamline biweekly labor reporting from 1 day to < 10 min.
- Developed a Django application that improved Special District audit compliance from 73% to 91%.
- Created an AWS Lambda service that reduced the delay in deposit notification from 1 day to 30 min.

### **Open Source Contributor** | Django | Jun 2020 – Present

- Implemented new features, optimized functionality, and wrote documentation/release notes.
- Participated in pull request reviews and collaborated with other developers to resolve issues.
- Executed Git workflow of checking out branches, squashing commits, and creating pull requests.

### PROJECTS

Sales Tax App | Santa Barbara Auditor-Controller's Office | Nov 2019 - Present

- Built a Django app to manage the deposit and allocation of 24 revenue sources totaling \$225.0 mil.
- Automated 25 hours of monthly workload to < 15 minutes and reduced the error rate by 95%.
- Executes GET requests to fetch CSVs, parses response, and builds accounting transaction XMLs.

### Inventory App | SneakrFlip.com | Mar 2020 - Present

- Built an inventory app using GoLang/React for reselling sneakers and other limited edition items.
- Implemented user authentication with oAuth bearer tokens and integrated Google social login.
- Deployed the backend/frontend on AWS EC2/S3 and set up an automated CI/CD pipeline via AWS.

#### Finance News Service | Twitter.com/StockNewsBot | Feb 2020 - Present

- Built a Twitter microservice using Node.js/AWS to send users daily tweets with finance articles.
- Implemented an Edit Distance DP algorithm to decide whether to reply to misspelled tweet actions.
- Built a Chrome Extension in React, Reddit bot in Python, and GUI in Java with similar functionality.

#### Real Estate App | Reinvestify.com | May 2019 - Present

- Built a full stack web app that generates reports on the profitability of real estate investments.
- Deployed the app on AWS, implemented a mortgage calculator, and introduced caching using Redis.

# **EDUCATION**

**Bachelors in Economics** | University of California, Santa Barbara | Jun 2017 **AWS Certified Developer - Associate** | Amazon Web Services, Cert #: ZGL37F0KMMF1QG5S | May 2020